<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Wedding on Wedding Kimi Go </title>
      <generator uri="https://hugo.spf13.com">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://nmcapule.github.io/kg/tags/wedding/index.xml/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <updated>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 19:50:22 PHT</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>SM Novaliches Bridal Exhibit</title>
      <link>http://nmcapule.github.io/kg/blog/second-entry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 19:50:22 PHT</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nmcapule.github.io/kg/blog/second-entry/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;SM Novaliches Bridal Exhibit&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PHILTRADE Exhibits was established in 2000 with the objective of supporting the Filipino enterprises through trade promotion like exhibitions, trade shows and special trade events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the last decade, it has done thematic exhibitions and has worked with organizations and associations all over the Philippines and abroad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an event management company, we believe that you can capture your public’s
and stakeholders through careful analysis and strategic execution of your marketing tools.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>blog/first entry</title>
      <link>http://nmcapule.github.io/kg/blog/first-entry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 19:17:14 PHT</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nmcapule.github.io/kg/blog/first-entry/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Crisologo - Valencirina Wedding&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When: November 27, 2010&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Where: Edsa Shangri-La&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>http://nmcapule.github.io/kg/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2014 20:53:21 PHT</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nmcapule.github.io/kg/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;About Us&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;KIMI GO, business established since 1992, serving various clienteles for their needs in casual, formal, and office/school uniforms with only three sewing machines as for our start At home. In late 1994, due to the big response of our customers, we open KIMI GO in Zamora St. Tondo Manila to accommodate the increasing number of our regular client.Since then, we been accepting made to order clothes formal, evening dress, and wedding gowns and uniforms for large and small scale establishments. Our clients for corporate uniforms, City College of Manila, Gotesco Ever Emporium maintenance dep’t, Facial Care Center, Bhoeringer Makati, Jollibee Tondo, K-9 Security Agency, Brills (Champ) Mandaluyong, Dental-B Ortigas office to mention a few. We are also serving ready to wear clothes to various department stores and boutiques in consignment. In 2002 we transfer to 1335 Juan Luna St. Tondo, Manila to hire additional manpower/sewer and eventually we also cater Photo and Video Coverage, Flowers, Souvenirs, wedding supply, Etc. And 2005 we acquire 541 Rubyville Property in Caloocan to use also receiving and office as second branch of KIMI GO One Stop Wedding Shop.Now last August 8, 2008 we open and acquire another commercial property located at Unit 1 Royalle Parthenon Square 685 Tandang Sora Ave. Quezon City as third branch. So our name KIMI GO is (16) sixteen years in the making and continuous to grow in the fashion industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Humble Beginnings&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What started as a home business with three sewing machines in 1992, Kimi established himself as a talent to reckoned with. Kimi’s diverse talent has allowed his business to expand to cater to a variety of clientele, creating office uniforms for small to medium scale business, Ready To Wear clothes consigned to various botiques on top of his highly specialised formal and evening wear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;The KimiGo Customer Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;KimiGo is synonymous with Bridal and Formal Gowns, which has become his niche in the market.“I want each client to be happy with every piece of item that I design and execute. Young girls come to my shop expecting to be transformed to a beautiful princess once they wear their gowns, Brides come to me with the faith that I will be able to create the prettiest wedding dress fitting of a lovely bride for their wedding day.. these expectations s what I have to fulfill. I want every women to be happy wearing the dress that I have designed and created for them.Not to be outdown, I want the bridegroom to feel the same. Our shop also execute Barongs and Tuxedo that are comfortable, stylish, easy to wear to match their partners outfit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_3&#34;&gt;Service to the Community&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of his outreach to the community, Kimi has been a Major Sponsor for various Beauty Pagents in Schools, Local Councils or Fashion Shows designing formal gowns or barongs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most recent projects includes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UST College of Education Dept of Food and Nutrition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flores de Mayo, Filipina La Bella Rosa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mutya ng Pilipinas 2005 and 2006&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maharlikang Pilipino&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;St. Mary’s College&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;St. Paul’s Manila&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>